<Language>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_EMPTY"></entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="RANDOMIZER_EMPTY"></entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_1">Just think of all the time you could save collecting geo with this.\n\nTime is money, right? Definitely worth it.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_2">If you can't keep your bearings without this you should probably just stop playing randomizer.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_3">What's better than being rewarded for getting hit? Amazing charm if you suck.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_4">Now all you need is quick slash, longnail, and mark of pride. Reddit's favorite charm build!\n\nReddit is never wrong, after all.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_5">It's like dreamshield, but cheaper and better at blocking damage.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_6">Sure, you COULD stay at 1 health with this, but a real gamer would stay at 2.\n\nDon't forget to pogo everything, too.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_7">Mickely's favorite charm.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_8">With this on, you'll be able to tank a whole two more hits. Amazing.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_9">Let's be honest, here. This isn't a progression item or a spell buff, so nobody will buy it.\n\nJust a waste of space, really.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_10">Haha poo.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_11">RIP Flukenest 2017-2018.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_12">It's a good thing thorn warps got patched so fast. Wouldn't want any cheaters in my randomizer.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_13">Three notches to slightly extend the range of my weakest attack? Sign me up!</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_14">You ever feel like you don't walk into enemies during combat enough? Well I have just the charm for you!</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_15">If you've got Kerr's charm modifications on, buying this could be a real blast.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_16">Such an amazing charm it has its own mod dedicated to it. What fool wouldn't buy this?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_17">Man it'd be a real bummer if you had to buy this garbage to leave Crossroads.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_18">This is technically enough to kill baldurs, but you're not that crazy.\n\nAt least I hope you aren't.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_19">You obviously want to buy this. But is it worth the cost?\n\n(Spoilers: yes.)</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_20">You'd have to be really hurting for damage to buy this, of all things.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_21">Who would ever use this charm? The effect is amazing, but come on. Four notches?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_22">Back in my day we had to jump through tunnels of spikes to get something like this.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_23">Wow two hearts? That's eight mask shards you don't have to collect.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_24">Gotta spend money to make money. I'm sure it'll pay for itself in no time at all.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_25">Wow this is a steal! Unbreakable normally adds 15k, so really you'd be a fool to not buy at this price.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_26">Who uses nail arts? Probably nobody now that the dash slash skips are gone.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_27">What do you mean I can't heal with this on?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_28">You want to turn into a snail? Of course not. This is a piece of garbage.\n\nSave your money for something else.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_29">Basically required to get through the hive alive. Better hope nothing is in there.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_30">Most people who play probably don't even know the dream nail gives you soul.\n\nMaybe that's why this is only one notch?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_31">Not worth the money unless you're using glitches. You're not a cheater, are you?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_32">Time to tank and spam nail. Strategy of champions.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_33">You know how this is normally surrounded by mistakes? Reminds me of anime.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_34">You ever wonder what it would be like if healing took so long you just get hit?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_35">Play lightbringer.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_36_L">That's right, I'm not even going to give you the full charm. That's how little I value your business.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_36_R">You want half of a charm? Well today is your lucky day!</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_36_Void">Don't worry about shade skips, I'm changing this to not modify shade behaviour.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_37">Go faster! But only when on the ground. And also only when walking. Oh and also it's a very minor speed boost.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_38">This should really be a one notch charm. Hell, even at one, I wouldn't use this.</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_39">This is a good charm after the buffs in Lifeblood, right?</entry>
    <entry sheet="UI" key="RANDOMIZER_CHARM_DESC_40">Most people would pay money to get rid of this trash, yet here you are contemplating spending money on it.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="RANDOMIZER_GET_CHARM_1_1">A swarm will follow the bearer and gather up any loose Geo.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="RANDOMIZER_GET_CHARM_1_2">Useful for those who can't bear to leave anything behind, no matter how insignificant.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="RANDOMIZER_BUTTON_DESC">You already know what to press</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="RANDOMIZER_EMPTY"></entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="JIJI_DOOR_KEY">This key may be required to enter waterways. Think hard before opening! Use simple key?</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="BATH_HOUSE_KEY">This key may be required to enter waterways. Think hard before opening! Use simple key?</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="NOT_ENOUGH_GEO">Not enough.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Elderbug" key="ELDERBUG_FLOWER_REQUEST">F-for me..? Senpai you're so kind.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Elderbug" key="ELDERBUG_FLOWER_REREQUEST">F-for me..? Senpai you're so kind.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Elderbug" key="ELDERBUG_FLOWER_ACCEPT">Thank you senpai!</entry>
    <entry sheet="Elderbug" key="ELDERBUG_FLOWER_DECLINE">O-oh...</entry>
    <entry sheet="Prompts" key="ELDERBUG_FLOWER">Give Elderbug-chan the flower?</entry>
    <entry sheet="Hornet" key="HORNET_GREENPATH">I'm not so hard? Are you kidding me?</entry>
    <entry sheet="MainMenu" key="VIDEO_VSYNC">Input Lag:</entry>
    <entry sheet="MainMenu" key="DESC_VSYNC">Leave on to make the game unplayable.</entry>
    <entry sheet="Titles" key="DIRTMOUTH_MAIN">Elderbug</entry>
    <entry sheet="Titles" key="DIRTMOUTH_SUB">is a cool dude</entry>
</Language>